Before me stands 'The Habits of a 4-Hour Golfer', a sign that seems to greet everyone who comes here for a game.
These few rules remind us of courtesy and strategy, making the game more enjoyable for everyone.
I leave them behind, heading to the main building of the 'Santa Teresa' club.
Reaching the main building, I meet players engrossed in tactical discussions.
Behind them are golf carts, prepared for play on the green expanses of the field.
Passing by the focused players, each absorbed in their game, I feel a connection with the past.
Golf, with its centuries-old history, originated in Scotland in the 15th century,
evolving from a simple game played by shepherds into a renowned global sport.
These fields bear witness to numerous strategies and strokes, honed over years and passed down through generations.
Here, where each swing of the club is written into history, every player continues an ancient tradition,
combining respect for the past with modern innovations of the game.